

CONTACT ME

+91 - 88986 - 13030

parab.neil25@gmail.com

in /narayan-parab

/parabneil

parabneil.github.io

Ambernath, Maharashtra, India.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Web Development
- HTML5 & CSS
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Material UI
- Python & Django
- MySQL & PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Git & GitHub
- Graphic Design
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking
- Active Listening
- Conflict Resolution
- Adaptability
- Creativity

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English

Hindi

Marathi

Konkani

NARAYAN PARAB

Software Developer



ABOUT ME

A Software Developer with experience specializing in user interface design, web application development, and continuous improvement. Proficient with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React JS. Most notably, created the setup for the organization's own react component library for reusable components. Adept at identifying opportunities to enhance the user experience and develop new features to improve app functionality.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2022 - Present

TEKNOBUILT

- Developed features from scratch for the organization's product as a full-stack resource in the development team.
- Built the reusable react component library for the organization in order to solve the problem of inconsistency of code.
- Collaborated with the project management teams to deliver new features on time and with the highest standard.
- Frequently used Git & GitHub to distribute and back up the codebase.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

2019 - 2022

ORNAMAX WEB SOLUTIONS

- Responsible for handling the various social media platforms for the organization's products and their promotions.
- Worked on creating the infographic images for the organization's social media pages and thumbnails for the youtube videos.

CONTENT WRITER

2017 - 2019

ORNAMAX WEB SOLUTIONS

- Responsible for writing informative blogs and articles for organization websites with engaging and SEO friendly content.
- Worked on creating the scripts and gathering the information about related topiscs for the organization's youtube videos.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

NEWTON SCHOOL

2014 - 2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE

UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI

The East Kalyan Welfare Society's Model College of Science & Commerce, Kalyan (E), Maharashtra, India

2012 - 2014

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (HSC) - COMPUTER SCIENCE

MAHARASHTRA STATE BOARD OF SECONDARY & HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION
The East Kalyan Welfare Society's Model College of Science & Commerce, Kalyan (E),
Maharashtra, India

2012

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (SSC)

MAHARASHTRA STATE BOARD OF SECONDARY & HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION Sudhagad Education Society High School, Kalamboli, Maharashtra, India.